Okay,this is it.
好，該結婚了
You sure you wanna do this?
你確定要這麼做？
Hello,Mrs. Ross.
你好，羅斯太太
Well,hello,Mr. Rachel.
你好，瑞秋先生
-Whoa! -Oh,my God!
我的天哪
Come on,Phoebe,hurry!
菲比快點！快快快
Okay! Okay!
好啦
Oh,my God! Is everybody getting married?
我的天哪！大家都要結婚嗎？
No running in the chapel.
教堂裡不准奔跑
Hey, don't you give me any of your.. Hey!
你少跟我來這…
Why are you here?
你們來幹什麼？
Ross and Rachel left a message. They're getting married.
羅斯和瑞秋留言說要結婚
-Isn't that why you guys are here? -Yes. Why else would we be here?
你們不是來找他們的嗎？ 當然是 不然我們來幹什麼？
What happened? Did we miss it?
怎麼樣？我們來晚了嗎？
We missed it.
我們也沒趕上
Maybe you wouldn't have if you could run in the chapel!
都是因為教堂裡不能奔跑
I can't believe they got married.
羅斯和瑞秋居然結婚了
I know! I didn't even know they were dating.
對啊，我還不知道他們復合了
I don't think they're as much dating as they are...
與其說是復合
...two bottles of vodka walking around in human form.
不如說是被伏特加附身
This is insane.
真是太扯了
What's the big deal? It's not like it's a real marriage.
有什麼關係？又不是真結婚
What?
什麼？
If you marry in Vegas, you're only married in Vegas.
在賭城結婚只有在賭城有效
If you marry here, you're married everywhere.
你在說什麼？ 在賭城結婚到處都有效
Really?
真的？
Yeah.
是啊
Oh,my God!
天哪…
Oh,well.
啊隨便啦
The One After Vegas
本集播出：「終身大代志」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Why are we in bed together?
我們為什麼躺在一起？
I don't know.
我不知道
-Did we? -I don't know.
我們有… 我不知道
Do you have any clothes on?
你有穿衣服嗎？
Yes.
有
-Really? -No.
真的？ 沒有
But we didn't have..
但是我們沒有…
...sex,did we?
嘿咻吧？
I don't remember much about last night.
我不太記得昨晚的事
It was such a blur.
一切都好模糊
I remember laughing. I laughed a lot.
我記得我有笑，我一直笑
Then we didn't have sex.
而且我們沒怎樣
Well,so,what did we do last night?
羅斯，我們昨晚做了什麼？
I don't know,but I think it was a lot of fun.
我不知道，但我覺得很開心
Luckily,not too much fun,right?
幸好沒有開心過頭
-I don't think so. -Oh,thank God.
應該沒有
Oh,I mean, we were really drunk.
我們真的醉得很慘
I'm glad we didn't do anything stupid.
幸好沒幹什麼蠢事
Tell me about it.
可不是嗎
（新婚大喜）
Morning,Phoebe.
菲比早
Well,my movie has been officially canceled.
我的電影取消拍攝了
Joey,I'm so sorry.
好可惜喔
You want my breakfast?
你要不要吃我的早餐？
Too depressed to eat.
不了，我沮喪得吃不下
I'll probably eat in, like, five minutes.
過5分鐘再說吧
I'll fly home with you. What time is your flight?
我只好跟你們回去了 飛機是幾點？
-What about my cab? -I don't need that anymore.
我的計程車呢？ 我用不著了
You borrowed my cab. You have to drive it back.
你跟我借車就要開回去
I don't wanna drive back by myself. I get lonely.
我不想自己開回去，太寂寞了
How about if you come with me?
乾脆你來陪我
-It's a long trip. -That would be great.
我不曉得，要開很久 一定很好玩
We could talk and play games.
我們可以聊天玩遊戲
This could be our chance to, like, renew our friendship.
這是讓友誼變新鮮的好機會
Are you asking me to have a "frienaissance"?
你要我跟你「友誼復興」？
Sure?
是吧？
All right. Although,I don't think we need one. I never stopped loving you.
好吧，雖然沒這個必要 我一直愛著你
So has anybody talked to Dr. and Mrs. Geller yet?
有誰跟蓋勒博士夫婦講過話？
They left me a message. They'll be here.
他們有留言給我，應該快到了
Where is the waitress? I'm starving.
服務生呢？我餓死了
It's a buffet,man.
這是自助餐
Here's where I win all my money back!
我可以撈本了
I gotta talk to you.
我有事找你
Sure.
好
What's up?
什麼事？
Monica and I almost got married.
摩妮卡和我昨晚差點結婚
My God!
天哪！
That's huge!
這可是大事
Wait a minute. Why wasn't I invited?
等等，為什麼沒找我去？
And who was gonna be your best man? Don't say Ross. Do not say Ross.
誰要當你的伴郎？ 不要說羅斯，不准說羅斯
I just don't think that Monica and I are ready yet. I love her...
我覺得我們還沒準備好 我很愛她
...but seeing Ross and Rachel come out of that chapel...
但看到羅斯他們從教堂冒出來
...was like a wake-up call that Monica and I are moving so fast, you know.
我突然驚覺我們進展得太快了
How do I tell her without crushing her?
我要怎麼講才不會讓她心碎？
Tell her she's not marriage material.
就說她不是結婚的料
What?
什麼？
Girls say it to me all the time.
女生都這麼對我說
And if she's anything like me, she's just gonna be relieved.
相信我，要是她和我一樣 一定會如釋重負
How do I tell him that it's too soon?
我該怎麼說這樣太快了？
He's gonna think I don't love him anymore.
他一定會心碎 覺得我不愛他了
-Well,you don't. -Yes,I do.
你是不愛他了 我愛
Good. I was just testing you.
很好，我只是在測試你
-Hey. -Oh,hi.
We were just talking about bacon.
我們才剛聊到培根
No,we were talking about tennis.
不對，我們是在聊網球
Tennis is more believable.
網球比較像真的
Thank you.
Coffee.
What?
怎樣？
Are we gonna talk about what you guys did last night?
你們要談談昨晚的事嗎？
What do you mean "last night"? Nothing happened last night.
昨晚什麼事？昨晚又沒怎樣
Ross invited us all to watch.
羅斯把大家都找去看了
What is the matter with you?
你有病啊？
We weren't gonna miss our friends getting married.
瑞秋 我們不可能錯過朋友的婚禮
Who got married?
誰結婚了？
You did.
你們啊
What?
什麼？
-Hello. We didn't get married. -No,we didn't. That's ridi..
我們哪有結婚 怎麼可能，別鬧了
Wait,wait,wait. I remember being in a chapel.
我們…我記得去過教堂
They would not let us get married when we were that drunk.
我們醉成那樣，不可能被批准
They let you get married.
當然可能
Most people who marry in Vegas are drunk.
在賭城結婚的人通常都醉了
Now,I'm drunk right now.
我現在就醉了
I can't have a mimosa with breakfast? I'm on vacation.
早餐不能喝雞尾酒啊？ 我在度假
What are you gonna do?
你們要怎麼辦？
Well, I guess we find a divorce lawyer.
看來得找個離婚律師了
Well, I think.. I think Ross already has one.
我想羅斯已經有一個了
Yeah, that guy's finally gonna be able to put in that pool.
他家總算可以蓋游泳池了
Okay.
好
Now,this one's free, right? Because you paid for the first two.
這次會免費吧？ 你辦了兩次，所以會送一次
Laugh it up,but the joke's on you...
你笑吧，丟臉的是你
...because we don't need to get divorced.
我們不必離婚
-We're just gonna get an annulment. -An annulment?
只要辦理註銷 註銷？
Ross,I don't think surgery is the answer here.
羅斯，手術可幫不了你
Oh,that's your thing!
那是你的正字標記
What?
什麼？
Your thing. You're the guy who gets divorced.
你的正字標記 你是專門離婚的人 沒錯
No,no,that's not "my thing."
那才不是我的正字標記
I do not love getting divorced.
我並不愛離婚
Yes,you do. This is your third divorce.
你當然愛，這是你第三次離婚
You love divorce so much, you're probably gonna marry it...
你愛離婚愛到搞不好會娶它
...and then it won't work out, so you're gonna have to divorce it.
然後婚姻破裂，你又得離婚 離婚名人
I'm so drunk.
我醉得好厲害
-You wanna play some Pai Gow? -Maybe.
要不要玩百高？ 也行
But I kind of think we should talk about last night.
但我有點想談談昨晚的事
That's a good idea. I wanna talk about last night too...
好主意，我也想談
-and I don't know what Pai Gow is. -I see.
而且我不知道百高是什麼
-So what should we do? -I don't know.
你覺得我們應該怎麼辦？ 不知道
I know I love you.
但我知道我愛你
我也知道我愛你
Where are we on the whole "going back...
那我們還要回過頭...
to where they have the marriages" thing? I love you.
...去結婚嗎？ 我愛你
That's a good question.
問得好
Last night we let the dice decide.
昨晚我們讓色子決定
We should leave it up to fate again. I love you!
也許應該再讓命運決定一次 我愛你
We don't get married unless there's a sign.
沒錯，有徵兆我們才結婚
So say...
要是...
you roll another eight, then there's a sign...
你又擲出八來 就表示...
that we should marry.
我們絕對應該結婚
Eight we get married...
好，八就結婚
but 2,3,4,5,6,7,9,10, 11,12,we don't get married.
二三四五六七九等等就不結
Sounds great.
聽起來不錯 好
Hey,we got a shooter.
有人要擲了
Money,please.
請押注
-Ready? -Ready.
好了嗎？ 好了
Come on,eight.
來個八吧
Yes,yes,eight.
沒錯，八
Eight,easy eight.
八，三五八
-I can't believe I rolled an eight. -That was so unlikely.
居然真的是八 真是太不可能了
Let's get married.
那就結婚吧…
I guess.
我猜
Last night I rolled a hard eight.
等等，那不是雙四八 我昨晚擲的是雙四八
It was the wrong kind of eight. No wedding! Damn it!
沒錯，這個八不對 不能結婚了，可惡
I wanted it so bad!
我好想結婚喔
Wanna go pack?
收拾行李去？ 好
We're doing the right thing.
我們沒做錯吧？
Of course we are.
當然沒錯
We left it up to fate.
我們讓命運決定
If we were supposed to get married, there would be a sign.
如果我們應該結婚 一定會有明確的徵兆
Okay,you have 19 questions left. Use them wisely.
好，你還剩十九個問題 要好好把握
Come on,Joey. You can't win if you don't ask any questions!
快點，你不問就…不能贏了！
-What? -You promised me a fun road trip.
怎樣啦 你說會很好玩
We've been on the road for 6 hours, and you've been asleep for 5 and a half.
結果我們開了6小時 你就睡了5個小時半
We are switching, and you are going to drive back.
下一個休息站就換手 你給我一路開回去
That will be your punishment, you greedy sleeper!
這是對你的懲罰，貪睡鬼
All right.
好啦
And until then,you are going to sing to me...
現在你得唱歌給我聽
...because the radio's broken and you are selfish, but you have a nice voice.
因為收音機壞了，你又很自私 但歌聲很好聽
-Really? -Sing!
是喔？我不… 快唱
I wanna rock 'n' roll all night
我想徹夜搖滾
Man,this is a long drive.
真是開也開不完
Are my eyes open?
我的眼睛有睜開嗎？
No!
沒有！
Morning.
早安
-Hey. -Hey,hubby.
老公
Actually,I wanted to talk to you about that whole annulment thing.
我想找你討論註銷婚姻的事
Yeah,I'm not gonna do that.
我不打算去辦
Okay.
好
So we'll just stay married.
那我們就維持婚姻關係
Yes,exactly.
沒錯
And I will make everyone call me Mrs. Geller.
我會請大家叫我蓋勒太太
Wow,this is so amazing.
真是太棒了
I really thought I'd have to talk you into this more.
我還以為得加把勁說服你
Now I'm scared because I don't actually think you're kidding.
我現在怕了 因為你好像不是在說笑
I'm not kidding.
我不是啊
Look...
...I can't have three failed marriages.
我不能有三次失敗的婚姻
I can't,okay?
我不能，好嗎？
I am not gonna be that guy.
我不要當那個人
Okay? No,no. That is not gonna be "my thing."
我不要有這個正字標記
So,what,we just stay married forever?
所以我們要永遠這樣下去？
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean,I haven't worked it all out yet,but....
我還沒想清楚
Okay,I know it's a bit crazy..
我知道這樣有點誇張
How is this going to affect you, really?
說真的，你有什麼影響？
I mean,you fill some form out once in a while...
偶爾填表格要打勾時
instead of checking the box "Miss," you check the box that says,"Mrs."
你就勾「已婚」那一格
It's right next to it.
就在「未婚」旁邊
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right. You know what?
好，抱歉，你說得對
We can stay married...
我們確實可以維持現狀
because I thought that the boxes were far away from each other.
我還以為那兩格離得很遠
-No, they're right.. -Ross!
不是… 羅斯！
All right. Just...
please take a moment here...
請你靜下來
and think about what you're asking of me. Okay?
想一想你在叫我做什麼
I am asking you to do me a favor.
我在請你幫我一個忙
You are asking me to be your wife.
你是要我當你的老婆
And as my wife,I think you should grant me this favor.
而身為我的老婆 你應該幫我這個忙
We did make vows.
我們發過誓了
That kid kicked me really hard.
那個小孩踢得好用力
Well,you did pull his hair.
是你扯他的頭髮
-He took my snack. -I'm not getting into this again.
他拿我的零食 我不想再爭了
All right,you know what? Hurts really bad.
好啦 說真的，真的很痛
Well,I told you not to walk. Here.
我就叫你不要走路，來
There. There. Okay.
來 來
-This doesn't mean anything,does it? -No.
這沒有任何含意吧？ 沒有
How could you pick up a hitchhiker?
你怎麼可以讓人搭便車？
He could be a rap.. He could be a rapist or a killer or something.
他搞不好是強… 強暴犯或殺人犯什麼的
Don't you think I asked him that before he got in?
你以為我沒有先問過嗎？
I'm not talking to you. You go back to sleep.
我不理你了，你睡你的覺
-And,you,are you a rapist? -No.
你，你是強暴犯嗎？ 不是
Do you like car games?
你喜歡車上遊戲嗎？
Yeah, you know the license plate game?
喜歡，你會牌照遊戲嗎？
I love the license plate game!
我最喜歡牌照遊戲了
I'll play. I'll play.
我也要玩，我也要玩
No, you need your sleep. Night-night.
不行，你需要睡眠，晚安
Listen. I know you wanted to talk to me...
聽著，我知道你想找我談
but I have an idea that may make you wanna stay married.
但我有個辦法 或許能讓你願意維持現狀
We register...
我們去註冊
and you get to keep all the presents.
禮物都給你
No, Ross, come on. No,listen.
不行！羅斯，你聽我說
I've thought about how to tell you this.
我一直在想要怎麼表達
I came up with an analogy about a little goldfish...
結果想到一個池塘裡的金魚
in a pond that freezes over in the winter...
在冬天凍死的比喻
but I realized that was a story about what to do when people pick on you.
後來又想到它是在談 如何面對別人的挑剔
So I'm gonna actually save that for my children's book.
那個故事我打算寫童話書時用
-What's up? -Oh,sorry.
怎樣？ 抱歉
The bottom line,Ross...
總之...
is we cannot stay married.
我們不能維持婚姻關係
-I don't know if that's true.. -Oh,but it is.
那可不一定 當然一定
Okay. You know what this is?
你知道嗎？
This is a difference of opinion.
這就叫做意見不合
-When that happens in a marriage.. -Ross,come on!
在婚姻中遇到這種狀況… 羅斯
This is not a marriage! This is the world's worst hangover!
這不是婚姻 這是全世界最慘的宿醉
Ross,listen, if you do not get this annulment, I will.
如果你不去註銷，我也會去
All right. All right,I'll do it.
好，我去就是了
Thank you.
謝謝
Hey,hey...
is there any such thing as an annulment shower?
對了 有沒有註銷婚姻送禮會？
There's the train station. This is where I get off.
等等，火車站在那裡 我該下車了
I have your address and phone number.
我有你的住址和電話號碼
I have your name and the fact that you're a drifter.
我知道你的名字和你居無定所
So ball's pretty much in your court.
主動權在你手上
All right. See you,Phoebe.
好，再見
Come on,Phoebe,I can't take this anymore.
拜託啦，我受不了了
Please talk to me.
求求你跟我說話
Let me make it up to you.
讓我補償你
Ground control to Major Tom
地面控制中心呼叫湯姆少校
Commencing countdown Engines on
倒數開始，發動引擎
Take your protein pills
吞幾顆蛋白質丸
And put your helmet on
戴上頭盔
-This is.. -Stop it! Stop it! No!
閉嘴，夠了
That's not fair. You know I can't resist that beautiful voice.
不公平，你明知我無法抗拒 那美妙的歌聲
Phoebe, look, I am so sorry.
菲比，我真的很抱歉
I promised you a fun road trip with your friend...
我答應讓你旅途愉快
and I didn't deliver,okay?
卻沒做到
Now I know that you think being awake is an important part of friendship.
現在我知道你認為保持清醒 對友情很重要
So I will strive to stay awake for as long as I know you.
以後我會永遠努力保持清醒
You can still sleep at night and stuff.
你晚上還是可以睡覺什麼的
Thank you.
謝謝
So can we play 20 Questions now?
那可以玩二十個問題了嗎？
I got a good one. I thought about it since Kansas.
我在堪薩斯就想到一題很棒的
Okay.
好吧
Is it...
是...
a kind of hot sandwich?
一種熱食三明治嗎？
Yes.
對
Is it a meatball sub?
是肉丸潛水艇嗎？
That is incredible!
真不可思議！
You are the master!
你是大師
Bug!
-Enough already! -Well, you didn't have to catch them!
真是夠了 誰叫你要接
-You look like you're.. -Don't say it!
真好玩，你看起來就像要… 別說了
Don't even think it.
想都別想
All right.
不說就不說
Chandler,enjoy your handful.
錢德，你跟她耗吧
Should we just get married?
我們要不要乾脆結婚算了？
All the signs are telling us to do it.
所有的徵兆都叫我們結
I'm sick of the signs.
我不想理徵兆了
-I'm happy the way things are. -Me too.
這樣太快了，我很滿意現狀 我也是
-I don't want change, do you? -No.
我不想改變，你想嗎？ 不想
Then nothing changes! Everything stays the same!
好，那就不要改變 一切維持現狀
Go unpack. It's been three days, and it drives me insane!
你快去整理行李 已經3天了，我快捉狂了
Jeez,relax,it's not like we're mar..
別激動，又不是要結…
You know,I was thinking, what if I...
要是我...
unpack here?
在這裡整理呢？
All your stuff would be here.
那你的東西都會在這裡
Well...
...what if all my stuff was here?
要是我的東西都在這裡呢？
Then you'd be going back and forth all the time.
那你就得跑來跑去
Doesn't make any sense.
沒道理嘛
Okay.
好
What if we live together, and you get what I'm saying?
要是我們同居呢？ 你懂我的意思吧？
Live together?
同居？
There've been no signs for that.
又沒有任何徵兆
Me asking is kind of a sign.
我問你就是個徵兆
Yes! Yes! Yes!
好！ 好！
Okay. Okay,wait. Wait,wait,wait.
好，你等等
Here's your key. Here's your key.
這是你的鑰匙
Now go out and christen it!
你得進行啟用式
Go out and come back in!
出去再進來
Door hasn't been locked in five years, but okay.
這扇門5年沒鎖了，不過好
-Ready? -Ready!
準備好了嗎？ 好了
The key broke in the lock, and I can't get in.
有點問題，鑰匙斷了我進不去
Wait. Oh,my God,I can't get out!
等等 我也出不去
-This isn't a sign! -No,it's a very old key!
這不是徵兆吧 不是，是鑰匙很舊了
-It's an old key! -Oh,my God,it's old!
鑰匙太舊了 舊得不得了
I love you.
我愛你
我也愛你
Are you hugging the door right now?
你有抱著門嗎？
No.
沒有
Yeah, yeah, me neither.
好，我也沒有
So did everything go all right with the annulment?
手續辦得還順利嗎？
Oh,yeah. No problems. It's all taken care of.
沒問題，都辦好了
Ross,thank you.
羅斯，謝謝你
Do you wanna go see a movie?
你們要不要去看電影
-Yeah, why not? -Phoebe?
好啊.  菲比？
No,thanks. I've already seen one.
不了，眼前就有一出
Okay,I'm gonna get my sweater.
我去穿毛衣 好
You wanna hear something weird?
想不想聽一件奇怪的事？
Always.
當然
I didn't get the annulment.
我沒去辦註銷
What?
什麼？
We're still married.
我們還是夫妻
Don't tell Rachel. See you later.
不要告訴瑞秋，待會兒見
獻給真的結婚的寇妮與大衛
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Key is stuck in the lock.
鑰匙斷在鑰匙孔裡
I can fix it. Hold on.
我會修，等一下
Watch out,watch out.
讓開
It still doesn't work.
還是打不開
I'm not finished.
我還沒弄完
Nice job, Joe. You're quite the craftsman!
漂亮，喬伊 你的技術真好